A Brand New Seven -- Doing Their Number! They put
their lives on the line and let it ride!
The Magnificent Seven Ride! is a western film directed by George McCowan.
Marshal Chris Adams turns down a friend's request to help stop
the depredations of a gang of Mexican bandits.
When his wife is killed by bank robbers and his friend is killed capturing the last thief, Chris feels obligated to take up his friend's cause and
recruits a writer and five prisoners to destroy the desperadoes.The last in the original series of four "Magnificent Seven" movies.
Marshal Chris Adams, played by Lee Van Cleef.
Mrs. Laurie Gunn, played by Stefanie Powers.
Noah Forbes, played by Michael Callan.
Arilla Adams, played by Mariette Hartley.
Mark Skinner, played by Luke Askew.
Pepe Carral, played by Pedro Armendáriz Jr..
The Magnificent Seven Ride!
(also known as The Magnificent Seven 4) is a 1972 American Western film and the
third and last sequel to the 1960 film The Magnificent Seven.
It stars Lee Van Cleef as Chris Adams, succeeding Yul
Brynner and George Kennedy in the role.
It was directed by George McCowan.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship,
dynamite, usa–mexico border, trap, sequel.